# **Dmitry Beskov**

#### Frontend developer

Tbilisi, Georgia | dmitry.beskov@outlook.com | besdar.github.io

#### Summary

I'm a React front-end developer with more than 4 years of experience. When I work, I usually point out the weaknesses in the company's processes and projects, and make suggestions to make our daily work more effective, fun and/or easier. I also try to fix code issues that I see on a regular basis. I really love what I do and I want to continue to grow in the frontend and create something great and special.

## Work experience

*IettyCloud (UCaaS)* May 2022 - Now

#### **Software Developer**

- Participating in the recruitment process and have developed a technical interview knowledge base for all roles across the company, which improved our interview process and made it easier to prepare for the technical interview
- Have created an account generation chrome extension for the company which greatly facilitates the daily work of both QA engineers and developers
- Mentoring junior front-end developers through code reviews and JS&TS syntax and code design explanation meetings
- · Simultaneously working in several teams and on several projects, never missed deadlines

In this role I usually creating, updating and maintaining various sub-modules for client account pages, internal admin pages

Stack: TS, React&Redux, Java&Kotlin, GraphQL

Foxford (EdTech) December 2020 - May 2022

#### Frontend developer

- Implemented code review for the team, was an organizer of frontend meetings
- Added large adjustment to the ESLint of a team project, added Stylelint, adjusted bundling and CI of the project
- Optimized IS code of the project and work process of the team developers now are writing faster and more stable code

Practically was a team leader, worked a lot with HTML&CSS and performed managerial activities like teamwork process optimization on various development stages

Stack: JS&FlowType, JQuery, HTML&CSS, React&Effector, NodeJS

BIOS (B2B, startup) April 2019 - December 2020

### Software developer

- Web-development: React and Redux / PHP / Typescript / 1C-Bitrix. Maintenence, project development. Self-education, selfrefactoring
- System administration: Configuring and deployment of (web-) servers and platforms (1C and others), OS errors resolving, project's git trees management
- Made Telegram client and TOTP algorithm two-factor authentication development for 1C platform

Was assigned and successfully resolved the most responsible and fundamental tasks, strictly followed the prescribed project timing, found solutions for various business tasks, independently set personal goals for further business improvement

Stack: React&Redux, HTML&CSS, JS, PHP, HTTP, NodeJS, 1C

#### **Education**

Saint Petersburg State Electrotechnical University 2014 - 2018

«Communication Technologies and Communication Systems»

**Faculty of Radio Engineering and Telecommunications**